{
    "subject": "Alan_Alda",
    "predicate": "actedIn",
    "object": "Sweet_Liberty",
    "human_readable": "Alan Alda acted in Sweet Liberty.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9861533641815186,
            "question": "What role did Alan Alda play in Sweet Liberty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8152097463607788,
            "question": "Who acted in Sweet Liberty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6347097158432007,
            "question": "Name a film starring Alan Alda."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5071044564247131,
            "question": "What film did Alan Alda act in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4920809268951416,
            "question": "Is Alan Alda known for any particular roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41597455739974976,
            "question": "In which movie did Alan Alda star?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4084968864917755,
            "question": "Besides acting, what else is Alan Alda known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22037558257579803,
            "question": "When was Sweet Liberty released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19035188853740692,
            "question": "What genre is Sweet Liberty?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18519975244998932,
            "question": "Are there any other films similar to Sweet Liberty?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alan Alda acted in Sweet Liberty.",
            "html": "yago_26400_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Sweet Liberty?",
            "html": "yago_26400_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Sweet Liberty released?",
            "html": "yago_26400_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides acting, what else is Alan Alda known for?",
            "html": "yago_26400_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26400_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26400_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26400_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26400_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26400_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26400_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26400_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26400_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26400_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26400_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The triple to evaluate is:\n\n\"Alan Alda acted in Sweet Liberty.\"\n\nGiven the context information, we can see that:\n\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_26400/re-ranker-msmarco/60.txt, it is mentioned that Alan Alda directed and starred in Sweet Liberty.\n* In file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_26400/re-ranker-msmarco/69.txt, it is explicitly stated that Alan Alda wrote and directed Sweet Liberty.\n* In multiple other files (e.g. file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_26400/re-ranker-msmarco/13.txt, 27.txt, 48.txt), it is mentioned that Alan Alda plays the lead role in Sweet Liberty.\n\nTherefore, the answer to the query \"Alan Alda acted in Sweet Liberty\" is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that Alan Alda directed and starred in the film \"Sweet Liberty,\" which directly supports the statement that Alan Alda acted in the movie."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}